# Tsung-Wei Ke

twke@berkeley.edu twke18.github.io

#### **Overview**

My research interest is in understanding the structures and contexts embedded in the image. My recent research is about representation learning for weakly supervised and unsupervised image segmentation. I've published several papers in the top-tier peer-reviewed conference in computer vision.

### **Education**

Ph.D. candidate, University of California, Berkeley, in Vision Science Program Computer vision and human vision, Advisor: Dr. Stella Yu B.S., National Taiwan University, in Chemical Engineering

## **Selected Publications**

Universal Weakly Supervised Segmentation by Pixel-to-Segment Contrastive Learning	
Tsung-Wei Ke, Jyh-Jing Hwang and Stell Yu	ICLR 2021
Adversarial Structure Matching for Structured Prediction Tasks	
Jyh-Jing Hwang*, Tsung-Wei Ke*, Jianbo Shi and Stella X. Yu	CVPR2019
Adaptive Affinity Field for Semantic Segmentation	
Tsung-Wei Ke*, Jyh-Jing Hwang*, Ziwei Liu and Stella X. Yu	ECCV2018
MultiGrid Neural Architecture	
Tsung-Wei Ke, Michael Maire and Stella X. Yu	CVPR2017
Mooney Face Classification And Prediction By Learning Across Tone	
Tsung-Wei Ke, Stella X. Yu and David Whitney	ICIP2017 oral
Mooney Faces from Photos	
Tsung-Wei Ke, Stella X. Yu and David Whitney	VSS2017 oral
Variational Convolutional Networks for Human-Centric Annotations	
Tsung-Wei Ke, Che-Wei Lin, Tyng-Luh Liu, Davi Geiger	ACCV2016 oral

#### **Appointments**

Appointments	
2021-2021:	Research Intern, Waymo LLC, Mountain View
2018-2020:	Research Fellow, University of California, Berkeley
	- participated in the project of animal detection and classification in wildlife with USGS
	- participated in the project of scene segmentation in aerial imagery with Samsung
2018, 2019:	Graduate Teaching Assistant, University of California, Berkeley
2016-2018:	Research Associate, International Computer Science Institute, Berkeley
	- participated in the project of material recognition in cityscape imagery with Samsung
	- participated in the project of particle screening for X-ray crystallography with NLBL